<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<details>
    <!-- Places details list -->
    <places>
        <place>
            <title>Adam’s Peak, for a mountain pilgrimage</title>
            <image>images/location1.webp</image>
            <description>Adam’s Peak is a tall, cone-shaped mountain in a diverse biological site in
                central Sri Lanka.
                The 2,243m (7,359ft) ascent is a common pilgrimage route in the Buddhist religion,
                as
                it’s said there is an impression of Buddha’s own footprint near the summit. It takes
                between two and four
                hours to climb; aim to arrive at the top around dawn for an unforgettable sunrise.</description>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Adam%27s_Peak</link>
        </place>
        <place>
            <title>Galle, for colonial architecture</title>
            <image>images/location2.webp</image>
            <description>Visit the well-preserved colonial city of Galle, on the southwest coast,
                for a
                relaxing city
                break full of charming Dutch-era villas and seaside views. Plan to see the
                Dutch-built
                Galle
                Fort – the largest remaining European-built sea fort in Asia and a World Heritage
                Site.
                Other
                highlights include the natural harbour, St Mary’s Cathedral, and Galle International
                Stadium,
                one of the most picturesque cricket grounds in the world.</description>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Galle_Fort</link>
        </place>
        <place>
            <title>Sigiriya, for a huge rock fortress</title>
            <image>images/location3.webp</image>
            <description>Sigiriya, also known as Lion Rock, is a rock fortress and palace in the
                Matale
                district. The Unesco World Heritage Site is one of the must-visit attractions in Sri
                Lanka. Climb up
                to the
                ancient ruins, which are surrounded by gardens, ponds, and magnificent frescoes, to
                see
                dramatic
                views of the jungle hills below.</description>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sigiriya</link>
        </place>
        <place>
            <title>Yala National Park, for spotting wildlife</title>
            <image>images/location4.webp</image>
            <description>Yala National Park, on the southeast coast, is the place to see big cats in
                Sri
                Lanka. The park
                is home to the highest concentration of leopards in the world, and it is also an
                important
                sanctuary for Sri Lankan elephants and aquatic birds. Monkeys, crocodiles and other
                creatures
                also run around the grassy plains and forest areas.</description>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yala_National_Park</link>
        </place>
        <place>
            <title>Polonnaruwa, for temple ruins</title>
            <image>images/location5.webp</image>
            <description>View fine examples of ancient Sinhalese art and architecture in the
                Unesco-protected town (and
                former Sri Lankan capital) of Polonnaruwa. It’s home to well-preserved ruins,
                including
                the
                12th-century Gal Vihara rock temple, the ancient site known as the Quadrangle, and
                the
                Buddhist
                Lankatilaka temple.</description>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Polonnaruwa</link>
        </place>
        <place>
            <title>The Cultural Triangle</title>
            <image>images/location6.webp</image>
            <description>In the central highlands is the Cultural Triangle, an area full of historic
                and
                religious
                remains. The main attractions are the temples of Anuradhapura and Polonaruwa, the
                rock
                top
                fortress of Sigiriya, and the cave temple at Dambulla. A must-visit is the Minneriya
                National
                Park, where elephants roam freely. There are some off-the-beaten-track temples and
                areas
                in the
                Cultural Triangle as well if you like to beat the crowds. To get to the area you can
                go
                by car
                or by train to Anuradhapura. Recommended by Orana Velarde.</description>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cultural_triangle</link>
        </place>
        <place>
            <title>Bentota, for laid-back vibes</title>
            <image>images/location7.webp</image>
            <description>This town on the southwest coast has magnificent beaches, luxury hotels and
                plenty of untouched
                beauty. Spend a day soaking in the sun at Bentota Beach, visit the nearby Kosgoda
                turtle
                hatchery or find peace in the Galapatha Rajamaha Viharaya Buddhist temple. Bentota
                is a
                tourist
                hotspot, so you’ll also be able to get stuck into activities such as helicopter
                rides
                and
                watersports.</description>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bentota</link>
        </place>
        <place>
            <title>Kandy, for seeing Buddha's Tooth</title>
            <image>images/location8.webp</image>
            <description>This large city is known as the Sacred City of Kandy for its significance
                to
                Buddhists. Many
                travel to the Temple of the Tooth, within the fourth-century royal palace complex,
                as
                it’s said
                to hold Buddha’s tooth – although you can’t actually see it. Elsewhere, Kandy is
                surrounded by
                the central highland mountains and is the placeto sample Sinhalese culture –
                especially
                if you
                visit during the Esala Perahera Festival in summer.</description>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kandy</link>
        </place>
        <place>
            <title>Nuwara Eliya, for tea plantations and mountains</title>
            <image>images/location9.webp</image>
            <description>Nuwara Eliya is a plateau town surrounded by mountains. It is also known as
                Little England for
                its British colonial buildings, such as the Queen’s Cottage and the General’s House.
                The
                area
                holds natural beauties, too, including waterfalls, hills, tea plantations, and
                Pidurutalagala,
                the tallest mountain in Sri Lanka. Nuwara Eliya is one of many tea plantation
                regions in
                Sri
                Lanka, but regarded as the most important tea producing spot in the country – try a
                cup
                on your
                visit.</description>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nuwara_Eliya</link>
        </place>
        <place>
            <title>Arugam Bay, for great surfing</title>
            <image>images/location10.webp</image>
            <description>Arugam Bay, on the southeast coast, is a remote town that attracts surfers
                from
                around the world.
                Brush up on your skills at one of the schools, such as Pappy’s Surf School or Amigo
                Surf, before
                heading out to the swell on Main Point. When not at the beach, visit the historic
                temples or the
                nearby Kumana National Park.</description>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arugam_Bay</link>
        </place>
        <place>
            <title>Dambulla, for seeing a cave temple</title>
            <image>images/location11.webp</image>
            <description>This large town is where to go in Sri Lanka to find the largest and
                best-preserved cave temple
                complex in the country. Covering a total area of 2,100sqm (22,604sqft), it has five
                cave
                temples
                containing a huge collection of Sri Lankan Buddhist artwork, including statues,
                shrines
                and
                murals. The paintings and statues tell stories from Buddha’s life – there are also
                153
                Buddha
                statues throughout the complex. Other statue subjects include Sri Lankan kings, gods
                and
                goddesses.</description>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dambulla</link>
        </place>
        <place>
            <title>Udawalawe National Park, for seeing elephants</title>
            <image>images/location12.webp</image>
            <description>It’s as though you’ve stepped into a wildlife documentary at Udawalawe
                National
                Park. The
                expansive sanctuary, on the borders of Uva and Sabaragamuwa provinces, is well and
                truly
                where
                to go in Sri Lanka for animal-lovers. Between October and April, you’re guaranteed
                to
                see
                elephants while in your 4×4 (since there are around 700 in the area). They share the
                park with
                leopards, crocodiles, water buffalos, otters and several species of eagle. The
                landscape
                varies
                as you go, with grasslands and scrublands complemented by rockier, more mountainous
                areas.</description>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Udawalawe_National_Park</link>
        </place>
        <place>
            <title>Mirissa, for beachside relaxation</title>
            <image>images/location13.webp</image>
            <description>Fancy hanging out in a hammock under the sun? Make your way to the
                beachside
                village of Mirissa
                on the south coast, best known for its sandy bays. The namesake beach is
                particularly
                popular,
                from which you can head out on a dolphin- and whale-watching boat trip between May
                and
                November.
                Coconut Tree Hill is also a must-visit destination to watch the sunrise.</description>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mirissa</link>
        </place>
        <place>
            <title>Colombo, for a bustling city break</title>
            <image>images/location14.webp</image>
            <description>Quick start your Sri Lankan adventure with a few nights in the capital.
                This
                west-coast
                metropolis has a skyline that comes alive at night, with the 350m (1,148ft) tall
                Lotus
                Tower
                perhaps the most impressive sight. Here, you can soak up sky-high views of Beira
                Lake
                from the
                observation deck, while tucking into a feast at the revolving restaurant. For
                natural
                beauty,
                head to Crow Island Beach Park and Viharamahadevi Park during the humid summer
                months.</description>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Colombo</link>
        </place>
        <place>
            <title>Ella, for the iconic Nine Arch Bridge</title>
            <image>images/location15.webp</image>
            <description>The mountainous town of Ella is best known for having the stone Nine Arch
                Bridge, between Ella
                and Demodara station, built by the British at the turn of the 20th century. You can
                take
                the
                journey from Kandy to Badulla or marvel at it with a trek through the surrounding
                jungle
                and tea
                plantations. This is where to go in Sri Lanka if you can never have too many hiking
                and
                photo
                opportunities – don’t miss waterfalls such as Bomburu Ella, which is the widest in
                Sri
                Lanka.</description>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nine_Arch_Bridge</link>
        </place>
        <place>
            <title>Anuradhapura, for ancient historical sites</title>
            <image>images/location16.webp</image>
            <description>Step back in time at the sacred city of Anuradhapura, which is one of the
                oldest inhabited cities
                in the world, perhaps dating back as far as the 10th century BCE. As you might
                expect,
                the
                ancient metropolis, surrounded by jungle and rice fields, is home to numerous
                historical
                sites;
                the most popular include the Ruwanwelisaya (featuring Buddhist relics) and
                Abhayagiri
                Stupa (a
                Buddhist monastery). Meanwhile, the sacred bodhi tree in the Mahamevn?wa Gardens is
                another
                place of pilgrimage, attracting thousands of visitors annually.</description>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anuradhapura</link>
        </place>
        <place>
            <title>Trincomalee, for beaches and diving</title>
            <image>images/location17.webp</image>
            <description>The port city of Trincomalee, on the northeast coast, is usually reached by
                train or bus from the
                capital – taking around seven hours. Once you’ve made it, put your feet up and enjoy
                sweeping
                beaches such as Uppuveli and Coral Cove, before spotting blue whales from Swami Rock
                Cliff. If
                you’re a keen diver, visit the Trincomalee Underwater Museum, off Sandy Bay Beach,
                to
                see
                sculptures and cannons.</description>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trincomalee</link>
        </place>
        <place>
            <title>Jaffna, for Temples, Forts and Markets</title>
            <image>images/location18.webp</image>
            <description>If you’re in the northern tip of Sri Lanka, spend a few days enjoying the
                sights and sounds of
                Jaffna, which is off the main tourist track. Cultural highlights include visiting
                the
                arches of
                the gilded Nallur Kandaswamy Hindu temple, which is one of the most significant
                Hindu
                temples in
                the country, and the Instagrammable Jaffna Fort, built in the 17th century by the
                Portuguese.
                More photogenic moments will be found at Jaffna Market, where you’ll find
                traditional
                sweet
                treats, colourful fruits and vegetables, and exotic souvenirs.</description>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jaffna</link>
        </place>
        <place>
            <title>Tangalle, for the best beaches in the country</title>
            <image>images/location19.webp</image>
            <description>Don’t forget to pack your beach gear if you’re heading to Tangalle. This
                coastal city, around
                three hours south of Colombo, has some of the most beautiful beaches in Sri Lanka,
                including the
                palm-fringed Tangalle Beach and Rekawa Beach, the latter being a top spot to watch
                turtles lay
                their eggs. If surfing is your thing, hit Hiriketiya Beach, which has year-round
                great
                waves for
                all abilities, including a more advanced reef break. Just fancy sunbathing and
                splashing
                around?
                Calmer waters are found at Goyambokka Beach.</description>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tangalle</link>
        </place>
    </places>

    <!-- Packages details list -->
    <packages>
        <package>
            <id>pk1</id>
            <title>Explore Coastal Sri Lanka – 10 Days</title>
            <image>images/pk1.jpg</image>
            <review>"Beautiful beaches and great hospitality." – Nuwan</review>
            <destinations>Bentota, Galle, Mirissa</destinations>
            <duration>10</duration>
            <price_old>1500</price_old>
            <price_new>1099</price_new>
            <type>Luxury</type>
            <stars>5</stars>
            <link>#</link>
        </package>

        <package>
            <id>pk2</id>
            <title>Hill Country Experience – 7 Days</title>
            <image>images/pk2.jpg</image>
            <review>"Tea plantations, cool weather, and breathtaking views." – Dinesh</review>
            <destinations>Kandy, Nuwara Eliya, Ella</destinations>
            <duration>7</duration>
            <price_old>1200</price_old>
            <price_new>999</price_new>
            <type>Luxury</type>
            <stars>5</stars>
            <link>#</link>
        </package>

        <package>
            <id>pk3</id>
            <title>Wildlife Safari Adventure – 5 Days</title>
            <image>images/pk3.png</image>
            <review>"Saw leopards, elephants, and more! Amazing tour." – Priya</review>
            <destinations>Yala, Udawalawe, Wilpattu</destinations>
            <duration>5</duration>
            <price_old>1000</price_old>
            <price_new>749</price_new>
            <type>Mid-range</type>
            <stars>4</stars>
            <link>#</link>
        </package>

        <package>
            <id>pk4</id>
            <title>Jaffna Heritage And Northern Culture – 7 Days</title>
            <image>images/pk4.jpg</image>
            <review>"Exploring the temples and culture in Jaffna was unforgettable." – Thilini</review>
            <destinations>Jaffna, Nallur, Casuarina Beach</destinations>
            <duration>7</duration>
            <price_old>1100</price_old>
            <price_new>999</price_new>
            <type>Mid-range</type>
            <stars>4</stars>
            <link>#</link>
        </package>

        <package>
            <id>pk5</id>
            <title>Ancient Cities Trail – 5 Days</title>
            <image>images/pk5.jpg</image>
            <review>"Walking through Polonnaruwa ruins was a magical experience." – Amith</review>
            <destinations>Polonnaruwa, Dambulla, Mihintale</destinations>
            <duration>5</duration>
            <price_old>980</price_old>
            <price_new>749</price_new>
            <type>Mid-range</type>
            <stars>4</stars>
            <link>#</link>
        </package>

        <package>
            <id>pk6</id>
            <title>Trincomalee Beach And Dive Retreat – 5 Days</title>
            <image>images/pk6.jpg</image>
            <review>"Snorkeling at Pigeon Island was the highlight of our trip!" – Nuwan</review>
            <destinations>Trincomalee, Nilaveli, Pigeon Island</destinations>
            <duration>5</duration>
            <price_old>950</price_old>
            <price_new>699</price_new>
            <type>Budget</type>
            <stars>3</stars>
            <link>#</link>
        </package>

        <package>
            <id>pk7</id>
            <title>Colombo City and Cultural Tour – 3 Days</title>
            <image>images/pk7.jpg</image>
            <review>"Short but sweet – perfect for a quick escape." – Ruwan</review>
            <destinations>Colombo, Kelaniya, Mount Lavinia</destinations>
            <duration>3</duration>
            <price_old>500</price_old>
            <price_new>399</price_new>
            <type>Budget</type>
            <stars>3</stars>
            <link>#</link>
        </package>

        <package>
            <id>pk8</id>
            <title>Sigiriya and Dambulla Discovery – 4 Days</title>
            <image>images/pk8.jpg</image>
            <review>"Climbing Sigiriya Rock was unforgettable!" – Meena</review>
            <destinations>Sigiriya, Dambulla, Minneriya</destinations>
            <duration>4</duration>
            <price_old>800</price_old>
            <price_new>599</price_new>
            <type>Mid-range</type>
            <stars>4</stars>
            <link>#</link>
        </package>

        <package>
            <id>pk9</id>
            <title>Whale Watching and Beach Escape – 6 Days</title>
            <image>images/pk9.jpg</image>
            <review>"Seeing blue whales in Mirissa was magical." – Tharindu</review>
            <destinations>Mirissa, Unawatuna, Galle</destinations>
            <duration>6</duration>
            <price_old>1300</price_old>
            <price_new>999</price_new>
            <type>Luxury</type>
            <stars>5</stars>
            <link>#</link>
        </package>

        <package>
            <id>pk10</id>
            <title>Tea Country Train Journey – 5 Days</title>
            <image>images/pk10.jpg</image>
            <review>"One of the most scenic train rides in the world." – Kasun</review>
            <destinations>Kandy, Nuwara Eliya, Ella</destinations>
            <duration>5</duration>
            <price_old>1100</price_old>
            <price_new>849</price_new>
            <type>Mid-range</type>
            <stars>4</stars>
            <link>#</link>
        </package>

        <package>
            <id>pk11</id>
            <title>East Coast Surf and Sun – 7 Days</title>
            <image>images/pk11.jpg</image>
            <review>"Great surf spots and chilled vibes." – Anya</review>
            <destinations>Arugam Bay, Passikudah, Kalkudah</destinations>
            <duration>7</duration>
            <price_old>1250</price_old>
            <price_new>949</price_new>
            <type>Mid-range</type>
            <stars>4</stars>
            <link>#</link>
        </package>

        <package>
            <id>pk12</id>
            <title>Cultural Triangle and Safari – 8 Days</title>
            <image>images/pk12.jpg</image>
            <review>"A mix of history and wildlife – best of both worlds." – Suresh</review>
            <destinations>Anuradhapura, Sigiriya, Minneriya</destinations>
            <duration>8</duration>
            <price_old>1450</price_old>
            <price_new>1099</price_new>
            <type>Luxury</type>
            <stars>5</stars>
            <link>#</link>
        </package>

        <package>
            <id>pk13</id>
            <title>Hiking and Waterfalls – 4 Days</title>
            <image>images/pk13.jpg</image>
            <review>"Bambarakanda Falls was absolutely stunning." – Rashmi</review>
            <destinations>Ella, Haputale, Ohiya</destinations>
            <duration>4</duration>
            <price_old>900</price_old>
            <price_new>649</price_new>
            <type>Budget</type>
            <stars>3</stars>
            <link>#</link>
        </package>

        <package>
            <id>pk14</id>
            <title>Luxury Beach Getaway – 5 Days</title>
            <image>images/pk14.jpg</image>
            <review>"The resort was paradise – worth every cent." – Shanika</review>
            <destinations>Bentota, Hikkaduwa</destinations>
            <duration>5</duration>
            <price_old>1400</price_old>
            <price_new>1199</price_new>
            <type>Luxury</type>
            <stars>5</stars>
            <link>#</link>
        </package>

        <package>
            <id>pk15</id>
            <title>Kalpitiya Dolphin Watching – 3 Days</title>
            <image>images/pk15.jpg</image>
            <review>"Hundreds of dolphins swimming alongside our boat." – Nadeesha</review>
            <destinations>Kalpitiya, Dutch Bay</destinations>
            <duration>3</duration>
            <price_old>700</price_old>
            <price_new>499</price_new>
            <type>Budget</type>
            <stars>3</stars>
            <link>#</link>
        </package>

        <package>
            <id>pk16</id>
            <title>Adam’s Peak Pilgrimage – 2 Days</title>
            <image>images/pk16.jpg</image>
            <review>"Climbing through the night was magical." – Harsha</review>
            <destinations>Adam’s Peak, Hatton</destinations>
            <duration>2</duration>
            <price_old>450</price_old>
            <price_new>349</price_new>
            <type>Budget</type>
            <stars>3</stars>
            <link>#</link>
        </package>

        <package>
            <id>pk17</id>
            <title>Rainforest Eco Adventure – 3 Days</title>
            <image>images/pk17.jpg</image>
            <review>"Sinharaja is a must-visit for nature lovers." – Mahesh</review>
            <destinations>Sinharaja, Deniyaya</destinations>
            <duration>3</duration>
            <price_old>650</price_old>
            <price_new>499</price_new>
            <type>Budget</type>
            <stars>3</stars>
            <link>#</link>
        </package>

        <package>
            <id>pk18</id>
            <title>Spiritual Temples Tour – 4 Days</title>
            <image>images/pk18.jpg</image>
            <review>"Peaceful and enlightening journey." – Malithi</review>
            <destinations>Kandy, Anuradhapura, Polonnaruwa</destinations>
            <duration>4</duration>
            <price_old>850</price_old>
            <price_new>649</price_new>
            <type>Mid-range</type>
            <stars>4</stars>
            <link>#</link>
        </package>

        <package>
            <id>pk19</id>
            <title>North-East Explorer – 9 Days</title>
            <image>images/pk19.jpg</image>
            <review>"Beautiful untouched beaches and culture." – Kavindu</review>
            <destinations>Jaffna, Trincomalee, Batticaloa</destinations>
            <duration>9</duration>
            <price_old>1600</price_old>
            <price_new>1249</price_new>
            <type>Luxury</type>
            <stars>5</stars>
            <link>#</link>
        </package>
    </packages>

    <!-- Reviews details list -->
    <testimonials>
        <testimonial>
            <img>https://i.pravatar.cc/100?img=12</img>
            <name>Touseeq Ijaz</name>
            <username>@touseeqijazweb</username>
            <text>A seamless booking process, comfortable transport, and gorgeous locations. I’ll
                definitely travel with them again.</text>
            <stars>5</stars>
        </testimonial>
        <testimonial>
            <img>https://i.pravatar.cc/100?img=1</img>
            <name>J.K Rowling</name>
            <username>@jkrowling</username>
            <text>I had a fantastic time in Sri Lanka. The agency handled everything smoothly, from
                airport pickup to jungle safaris!</text>
            <stars>4</stars>
        </testimonial>
        <testimonial>
            <img>https://i.pravatar.cc/100?img=3</img>
            <name>Harry Potter</name>
            <username>@danielredclifd</username>
            <text>From the ancient cities to the southern beaches, every moment was unforgettable.
                Great service and support from the team!</text>
            <stars>5</stars>
        </testimonial>
        <testimonial>
            <img>https://i.pravatar.cc/100?img=5</img>
            <name>Oliva</name>
            <username>@olivaadward</username>
            <text>Wonderful experience! The team was super friendly and helped us discover hidden
                gems across Sri Lanka. Highly recommend!</text>
            <stars>4</stars>
        </testimonial>
        <testimonial>
            <img>https://i.pravatar.cc/100?img=9</img>
            <name>Liam K.</name>
            <username>@liam_travels</username>
            <text>Amazing experience with this agency! Everything was perfectly organized, and I
                felt safe and relaxed the whole time.</text>
            <stars>5</stars>
        </testimonial>
        <testimonial>
            <img>https://i.pravatar.cc/100?img=15</img>
            <name>Sofia R.</name>
            <username>@sofia_globetrotter</username>
            <text>Loved every moment of the Sri Lanka tour! The cultural sites and beach resorts
                were unforgettable. Highly recommend!</text>
            <stars>4</stars>
        </testimonial>
    </testimonials>
</details>